{"data":[{"question":"___ cooking we must work hard at it.","a":"In order to have a good command of","b":"So as have a good command of","c":"So to have a good command of","d":"As to have a good command of","answer":"1","explain":"\n- In order to + Infinitive = So as to + Infinitive: implies the purpose of doing sth","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"That life guard did everything he could ___ the drowning child.","a":"save","b":"to save","c":"saved","d":"saving","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To + Infinitive: implies the purpose of an action (did everything he could)","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"_________ for several weeks, the whole province was short of food, clothing and electricity.","a":"As flooding","b":"As having flooded","c":"Being flooded","d":"Having been flooded","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Passive voice- past perfect tense \n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"___ as a serious coach, Robert is respected by all the players in his team.","a":"Having known","b":"Knowing","c":"To know","d":"Known","answer":"4","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"___ tomorrow's test, I have no time to go out with you.","a":"Not prepare","b":"Not preparing","c":"Not having prepared","d":"Not being prepared","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"___ his manners, David put his feet up to the table.","a":"Forgetting","b":"Forgotten","c":"To forget","d":"Being forgetting","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Present perfect tense \n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"___ more time, I must be able to work out all the grammar problems.","a":"Giving","b":"Given","c":"Gave","d":"To give","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase ","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"___ you the truth, I didn't want to tell you about it.","a":"Telling","b":"To tell","c":"Told","d":"To be told","answer":"2","explain":"\n- To + Infinitive: imply the purpose of an action","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"___ from his looks, he could be a kind man.","a":"Being judged","b":"Judging","c":"Judge","d":"To judge","answer":"2","explain":"\n- A participle is a verb form which can be used as an adjective to describe a noun \n+When the present participle (-ing from) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) the performer of the activity named by the participle \n+ When the past participle (-ed, -en form) is used, the noun it describes is (or was) acted upon \n- When a participial phrase begins a sentence, a comma should be placed after the phrase","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"},{"question":"I am sorry ___ you so much trouble. And thank you for your help.","a":"to have given","b":"to give","c":"gave","d":"giving","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Sorry to do: is not occurring or imminent \n- Sorry for doing: what had happened","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"73","subcategorylv2":"16","type":"1"}]}